// See instructions at the bottom of the file...


// SAMPLE FILE ONLY! PLEASE COMPLETE BEFORE USING!

-->DE-CH
TallyJ|Contrôle9

-->DE
TallyJ|Zählen9
EN|Englisch
DE|Deutsch
FR|Français
DE-CH|Schweizer Deutscher

Overview|Überblick
OverviewLink|Überblic<u>k</u>
OverviewAccessKey|K





///////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
// Comments are started with //

// Please read this entire section before starting!

// Two steps to translations:
//  1. Make a new copy of a Phrases_XX.txt (usually the EN) file. Name it to match the language translation
//     being made, eg: Phrases_DE.txt for German.
//     Make a new Language section (-->xx) in this file. Put one line of text for each line in the EN file.
//     Any phrase that is not included in a Language section will default to what is in the EN section of the EN file.
//     Always define a main language (eg: FR) and then, if desired, define any differences in a sub-language code.

//  2. Translate the text in any .htm file that ends with _EN.htm in a copy of that file, named as above.
//     If a "sub" language is being used, a separate .htm file is needed for each language variation.
//     If no translated file is found, the _EN version will be used.

// Define a language section in a language file with
//       -->LANGCODE-SUBLANGCODE
// The language codes are defined by whoever does the translation. However, please follow the guidelines
// for codes as found at
//     http://users.pandora.be/linefeed/FastReferences/Countries.html
// or  http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/default.asp?url=/library/en-us/csvr2002/htm/cs_rp_appcfg_lism_c.asp

// If a sub language code is being defined (eg. FR-CA) then it MUST be listed BEFORE a plain FR code in the FR file.
// Only phrases that are different in FR-CA from what is in FR need to be included.
// The main language section must come after sub-language sections, as it is used for the default if a phrase 
//   is not matched in the sub-language.

// Format of each phrase line:
//       Key | Value
//  or
//       Key

// If  Value  is not provided, the text of the Key is used directly (generally useful only for EN).
// If you are translating from English and there is no | on the line, add one, followed by the translation.
// Do not ever change any Key! The program code references the Key exactly as found in the EN section.
// The Key is not case sensitive.

// If a phrase is not found in the language file or the EN file, say for "FileName", then "??FileName??" will 
// appear in TallyJ.

// After saving changes to this file, reload TallyJ (press F5) to see the results. Click on the Version number 
// displayed near the top-right corner to view a display of the translation results.

